Guide to the Seattle Department of Parks and Recreation Planning, Construction and Maintenance Records 1928-1994
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Project files, 1928-1994
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park - Design Development, undated (Box-folder 55/7)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park - Environmental Impact Statement, 1972 (Box-folder 55/8)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park - Presentations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 55/9)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park - Interagency Committee Outdoor Recreation Application, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 55/10)
  - Waterfront: Railroad Study, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 55/11)
  - Waterfront: Railroad Study, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/12)
  - Waterfront Parking Study, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 55/13)
  - Waterfront - Central Waterfront Park - Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 55/14)
  - Waterfront: Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 55/15)
  - Waterfront: Seattle Steam Corporation, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 55/16)
  - Waterfront: Street Vacation Undergrounding, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 55/17)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 55/18)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park - Property Acquisition, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 55/19)
  - Waterfront: Mayor's Waterfront Advisory Committee (1), 1969 (Box-folder 55/20)
  - Waterfront: Mayor's Waterfront Advisory Committee (2), 1969 (Box-folder 55/21)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Marine, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 55/22)
  - Waterfront: World Trade Center Studies, 1969 (Box-folder 55/23)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Private Development Proposals, 1970 (Box-folder 55/24)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Association, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 55/25)
  - Waterfront: Citizen's Response to Alternate Policies, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 55/26)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Study Project Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 56/1)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Study Reports Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder 56/2)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Study (includes correspondence meeting reports), 1969 (Box-folder 56/3)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Study, 1970 (Box-folder 56/4)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Study, 1970 (Box-folder 56/5)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 56/6)
  - Waterfront: Citizen's Waterfront Task Force Meeting Minutes Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder 56/7)
  - Waterfront: Citizen's Waterfront Task Force, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 56/8)
  - Waterfront: Citizen's Waterfront Task Force Reports, 1971 (Box-folder 56/9)
  - Waterfront Park, 1972 (Box-folder 56/10)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park, 1972 (Box-folder 56/11)
  - Waterfront: Reports Studies, 1973 (Box-folder 56/12)
  - Waterfront: Park Phase I Addendum to Draft EIS, 1973 (Box-folder 56/13)
  - Waterfront: Central Waterfront Park, 1973 (Box-folder 56/14)
  - Waterfront Park, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 56/15)
  - Waterfront: Drawings Aerial Map, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 56/16)
  - Waterfront Park - Street Improvements, 1977 (Box-folder 56/17)
  - Waterfront Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 56/18)
  - Waterfront: Pier 59 Structural and Piling Surveys, 1975 (Box-folder 57/1)
  - Waterfront: Italian Community Hall Donation / Columbus Statue, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 57/2)
  - Waterfront: San Mateo Steam Ferry, 1973 (Box-folder 57/3)
  - Waterfront: San Mateo Steam Ferry, 1974 (Box-folder 57/4)
  - Waterfront: San Mateo Steam Ferry, 1975 (Box-folder 57/5)
  - Waterfront: San Mateo Steam Ferry - newspaper clippings, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 57/6)
  - Westcrest Park (West Seattle Reservoir) - Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 57/7)
  - Westcrest Park ( West Seattle Reservoir), 1969-1975 (Box-folder 57/8)
  - Westcrest Park - Agreements Contracts, 1975 (Box-folder 57/9)
  - Westcrest Park (West Seattle Reservoir), 1976-1978 (Box-folder 57/10)
  - Westlake Mall Park, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 57/11)
  - Westlake Mall Park, 1971 (Box-folder 57/12)
  - Westlake Mall Park, 1972 (Box-folder 57/13)
  - Westlake Mall Park (includes Westlake Park Advisory Committee Minutes), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 57/14)
  - Westlake Mall Park, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 57/15)
  - Westlake Mall Park: Newspaper Clippings, 1969-1979 (Box-folder 57/16)
  - West Queen Anne Play Parks, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 57/17)
  - West Queen Anne Play Areas: Bayview and Kinnear, 1982 (Box-folder 57/18)
  - West Queen Anne Play Areas: Bayview and Kinnear, 1983 (Box-folder 57/19)
  - West Queen Anne Play Parks - Coe Elementary School, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 57/20)
  - West Queen Anne Soundview Terrace Contracts Agreements, 1973 (Box-folder 57/21)
  - West Queen Anne - Soundview Terrace, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 57/22)
  - West Queen Anne Parks - Soundview Terrace, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 57/23)
  - West Queen Anne Hill Parks - Soundview Terrace Contracts Agreements, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 57/24)
  - West Queen Anne Play Parks - 12th and Howe, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 57/25)
  - West Queen Anne Play Parks - 12th and Howe, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 57/26)
  - West Queen Anne Play Parks - 12th and Howe Contracts Agreements, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 57/27)
  - West Queen Anne Playfield Expansion, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 58/1)
  - West Queen Anne Playfield Expansion - Planning and Program, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 58/2)
  - West Queen Anne Playfield Expansion - Maps and Drawings, 1971 (Box-folder 58/3)
  - West Queen Anne Playfield Expansion, 1969 (Box-folder 58/4)
  - West Queen Anne Playfield Expansion, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 58/5)
  - West Queen Anne Playfield Expansion, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 58/6)
  - West Queen Anne School Playground, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 58/7)
  - Queen Anne Parks Recreation Committee Survey, 1970 (Box-folder 58/8)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion - Project Description Acquisition, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 58/9)
  - West Seattle Golf Course, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 58/10)
  - West Seattle Golf Course - Funding, 1971 (Box-folder 58/11)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion - Contracts and Drawings, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 58/12)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion - Planning Program, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 58/13)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 58/14)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 58/15)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion - Reports, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 58/16)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion - Longfellow Creek Basin, 1976 (Box-folder 58/17)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion, 1972 (Box-folder 58/18)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion, 1973 (Box-folder 58/19)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 58/20)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion, 1977 (Box-folder 58/21)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion - Contracts Agreements, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 58/22)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Expansion, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 58/23)
  - West Seattle Golf Course Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/24)
  - West Seattle Stadium, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 58/25)
  - West Seattle Stadium, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 58/26)
  - West Seattle Stadium, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 58/27)
  - West Seattle Stadium, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 58/28)
  - Yesler Atlantic Pedestrian Pathway, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 59/1)
  - Yesler Atlantic Pedestrian Pathway - Drawings, 1970 (Box-folder 59/2)
  - Yesler Atlantic Pedestrian Pathway, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 59/3)
  - Yesler Atlantic / Pratt Fine Arts Center, 1976 (Box-folder 59/4)
  - Yesler Atlantic Park and Recreation Center, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 59/5)
  - Yesler Neighborhood Center / Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 59/6)
  - Yesler Atlantic - Operation Breakthrough, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 59/7)
  - Yesler Atlantic Park and Recreation Center Drawings Plans (includes Operation Breakthrough), 1971 (Box-folder 59/8)
  - Yesler Atlantic Park and Recreation Area, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 59/9)
  - Yesler Atlantic Park and Recreation Area, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 59/10)
  - Yesler Atlantic Park and Recreation Center, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 59/11)
  - Yesler Atlantic Park and Recreation Center (includes Fine Arts Center / Pratt Park), 1975-1978 (Box-folder 59/12)
  - Yesler Atlantic Park Recreation Area Contracts Agreements, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 59/13)
  - Yesler Atlantic Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 59/14)
  - 37th Avenue South Comfort Station Drawings, 1983 (Box-folder 59/15)
  - Aquarium - South Apron Security Doors Drawings, 1986 (Box-folder 59/16)
  - Beacon Hill Playfield, 1970 (Box-folder 59/17)
  - Bitter Lake Community Center Siting, 1992 (Box-folder 59/18)
  - Burke Gilman Place (Includes Drawings), 1983 (Box-folder 59/19)
  - Burke Gilman Place, Slides of Drawings, undated (Box-folder 59/20)
  - Burke Gilman Trail Drainage Study, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 59/21)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield (Incl. Drawings), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 59/22)
  - City Wide Infrastructure #459, Four Site Drainage Improvements (Incl. Drawings), 1985-1988 (Box-folder 59/23)
  - Concrete / Asphalt Paving Repair, 1992 (Box-folder 59/24)
  - Discovery Park Demolition of Buildings, 1980 (Box-folder 60/1)
  - Discovery Park Demolition of Buildings, Field Reports, 1981 (Box-folder 60/2)
  - Discovery Park Modified Entry Road, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 60/3)
  - Freeway Park Drainage, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 60/4)
  - Freeway Park Drainage, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 60/5)
  - Freeway Park Drainage Drawings, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 60/6)
  - Freeway Park Drainage Investigation Report, 1988 (Box-folder 60/7)
  - Garfield Playfield (Incl. Drawings), 1985 (Box-folder 60/8)
  - Hiawatha and Jefferson Playfield Lighting, 1980 (Box-folder 60/9)
  - I-90 Lid Park, 1994 (Box-folder 60/10)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 60/11)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center, Asbestos Abatement (542)61, 1990 (Box-folder 60/12)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center, Drawings, 1971 (Box-folder 60/13)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center, Facility Upgrade Report, undated (Box-folder 60/14)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center, Photos, 1991 (Box-folder 60/15)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center, Property, 1991 (Box-folder 60/16)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center Roof Replacement and Seismic Stabilization (712), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 60/17)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center Roof Replacement and Seismic Stabilization (712), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 60/18)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Arts Center Roof Replacement and Seismic Stabilization (712), 1991-1992 (Box-folder 60/19)
  - Lower Woodland Sportsfield Rehabilitation, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 60/20)
  - Madrona Playground and Dearborn Park Rehabilitation Phase II, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 60/21)
  - Magnolia and Miller Community Centers Improvements (716), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 60/22)
  - Magnolia and Miller Community Centers Improvements (716), 1987-1990 (Box-folder 60/23)
  - Market Park, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 60/24)
  - MOHAI Interior Renovation Re-Roof, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 61/1)
  - MOHAI Interior Renovation Re-Roof, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 61/2)
  - North Acres Park, 1973 (Box-folder 61/3)
  - North Acres Shelter House II, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 61/4)
  - NE Queen Anne Park, 1974 (Box-folder 61/5)
  - Occidental Park Kiosk Engineering Drawings, 1992 (Box-folder 61/6)
  - Occidental Square Park Renovation, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 61/7)
  - Occidental Square Park Renovation, 1992 (Box-folder 61/8)
  - Occidental Square Park Revision (Pergola Modifications), 1992 (Box-folder 61/9)
  - Occidental Square Park Revision (Pergola Modifications), 1992 (Box-folder 61/10)
  - Occidental Square Park Renovations, 1992 (Box-folder 61/11)
  - Pier 57 East Half Renovation (Incl. Drawings), 1983-1984 (Box-folder 61/12)
  - Pier 62 Art Fence (Incl. Photographs), 1990 (Box-folder 61/13)
  - Pier 62 / 63 Seattle Junior Chamber of Commerce Improvements, 1992 (Box-folder 61/14)
  - Pier 62 / 63 Seattle Junior Chamber of Commerce Proposal, 1993 (Box-folder 61/15)
  - Pier 62 / 63 Seattle Junior Chamber of Commerce Proposed Improvements, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 61/16)
  - Piling Replacements, Gas Works Park, Leschi Moorage, Seward Park, etc. (Incl. Drawings), 1976-1980 (Box-folder 61/17)
  - Pioneer Square Pergola Repairs, 1993 (Box-folder 61/18)
  - Prefontaine Place Improvements (Incl. Drawings), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 61/19)
  - Rainier Recreation Center Gym Floor, 1974 (Box-folder 61/20)
  - Roofing - Alki Community Center (Incl. Drawings), 1993 (Box-folder 61/21)
  - Roofing - Alki Community Center (Incl. Drawings and Photographs), 1993 (Box-folder 61/22)
  - Roofing - Bitter Lake Community Center, 1988 (Box-folder 61/23)
  - Roofing - High Point Community Center Gymnasium (Incl. Photographs), 1990 (Box-folder 61/24)
  - Roofing - Magnolia Community Center Gym, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 61/25)
  - Roofing - Magnolia Community Center Gym Inspection (Incl. Photographs), 1990 (Box-folder 61/26)
  - Roofing - Magnolia and Lake City Community Centers, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 62/1)
  - Roofing - Magnolia and Lake City Community Centers Drawings, 1988 (Box-folder 62/2)
  - Roofing - Montlake Community Center Schematic Design, 1987 (Box-folder 62/3)
  - Roofing - Montlake Community Center (Incl. Drawings), 1988 (Box-folder 62/4)
  - Roofing - Montlake Community Center (Incl. Photographs), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 62/5)
  - Roofing - Pratt Fine Arts Center, 1990 (Box-folder 62/6)
  - Roofing - Pratt Fine Arts Center, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 62/7)
  - Roofing - Queen Anne Pool (Incl. Photographs), 1990-1992 (Box-folder 62/8)
  - Roofing - Queen Anne Pool, 1990 (Box-folder 62/9)
  - Roofing - Queen Anne Pool, 1990 (Box-folder 62/10)
  - Roofing - Rainier Community Center (Incl. Drawings), 1988-1991 (Box-folder 62/11)
  - Roy Street Carpentry Shop Ventilation, 1991 (Box-folder 62/12)
  - Seattle Art Museum Skylight Replacement Drawings, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 62/13)
  - Seward Park Roads and Paving Project, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 62/14)
  - Seward Park Roads and Paving Project, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 62/15)
  - Seward Park Roads and Paving Project, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 62/16)
  - Soundview Terrace / West Queen Anne Neighborhood Parks (Inc. Drawings), 1982 (Box-folder 62/17)
  - Swimming Pools: Madison, etc. Heating (Incl. Drawings), 1981-1982 (Box-folder 62/18)
  - Urban Recreation Barrier Removal - Alki Beach, Atlantic City Park and Volunteer Park, 1982 (Box-folder 62/19)
  - Van Asselt Community Center Improvements Drawings, 1984 (Box-folder 62/20)
  - Wallingford Playfield Improvements (Incl. Drawings), 1984 (Box-folder 62/21)
  - Waterfront Park Renovations, Piers 57-59 Phase II (774) (Incl. Photographs), 1987-1988 (Box-folder 63/1)
  - Waterfront Park Renovations, Piers 57-59 Phase II (774), 1988 (Box-folder 63/2)
  - Waterfront Park Renovations, Piers 57-59 Phase II (774), 1987 (Box-folder 63/3)
  - West Seattle Stadium Slope Restoration (Incl. Drawings and Photographs), 1985-1991 (Box-folder 63/4)
  - Westlake Park Project, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 63/5)
  - Westlake Park - Draft Audit, 1989 (Box-folder 63/6)
  - Westlake Park - Draft Audit, 1990 (Box-folder 63/7)
  - Westlake Park - Draft Audit Report, 1990 (Box-folder 63/8)
  - Westlake Park - Design and Construction Administration Audit, 1991 (Box-folder 63/9)
  - Westlake Park - Design and Construction Administration Audit, 1991 (Box-folder 63/10)
  - Westlake Park - Design Contract History, 1988 (Box-folder 63/11)
  - Westlake Park Project, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 63/12)
  - Westlake Park Handrail - Photographs and Drawing, 1989 (Box-folder 63/13)
  - Westlake Park Slides, undated (Box-folder 63/14)
  - Westlake Park Photographs, undated (Box-folder 63/15)
  - Westlake Park Waterfall Video, undated (Box-folder 63/16)
  - Woodland Park Landscape, 1979 (Box-folder 63/17)
  - Zoo Education Center, (Incl Drawings), 1981 (Box-folder 63/18)
  - Zoo Hippo Viewing Area Expansion (Incl. Drawings), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 63/19)
  - Zoo Holding Cages, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 63/20)
  - Zoo Maned Wolf Area, 1981 (Box-folder 63/21)
  - Zoo Small Mammal Grotto, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 63/22)
  - Zoo Snow Leopard Exhibit / Feline House (Incl. Drawings), 1981-1984 (Box-folder 63/23)
  - Westlake Park Drawings, 1988 (Box-folder 64/1)
- Planning files, 1961/1984
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, Burlington-Northern Right-of-Way, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 65/1)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, Burlington-Northern Right-of-Way, 1972 (Box-folder 65/2)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 65/3)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail Right-of-Way, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 65/4)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, Potential Acquisitions From Burlington Northern, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 65/5)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 65/6)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, Ackerly Communications (Incl. Photographs), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 65/7)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, Contract and Reports, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 65/8)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail EIS, 1974 (Box-folder 65/9)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, Jeanette Williams et. Al., 1982-1984 (Box-folder 65/10)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, NE 97th to 100th Area (Incl. Photographs and Drawings), 1976-1984 (Box-folder 65/11)
  - Burke - Gilman Trail, Riviera Pl. NE, 1961-1980 (Box-folder 65/12)
  - Discovery Park Archaeological Survey, Scope of Work, 1981 (Box-folder 65/13)
  - Discovery Park Coast Guard Antenna Site, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 65/14)
  - Discovery Park, HD and MF SEIS Appeals (Margaret Coughlin et al), 1983 (Box-folder 65/15)
  - Discovery Park, Public Hearing Transcript, 1981 (Box-folder 65/16)
  - Discovery Park Historic District Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 65/17)
  - Discovery Park Historic District Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 65/18)
  - Discovery Park Historic District Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 65/19)
  - Discovery Park Historic District Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 65/20)
  - Discovery Park Historic District Correspondence, 1981 (Box-folder 65/21)
  - Discovery Park Historic District, 1978 (Box-folder 65/22)
  - Discovery Park Historic District, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 65/23)
  - Discovery Park Historic District, Ft Lawton Adaptive Reuse SEIS Attachments, undated (Box-folder 65/24)
  - Discovery Park, Margaret Coughlin, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 66/1)
  - Discovery Park, North Beach Trail, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 66/2)
  - Discovery Park, North Beach Trail, 1981 (Box-folder 66/3)
  - Discovery Park, North Beach Trail, undated (Box-folder 66/4)
  - Discovery Park, Plan Maps, 1983 (Box-folder 66/5)
  - Discovery Park Planning / Planner, 1969 (Box-folder 66/6)
  - Discovery Park, Rhododendron Society, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 66/7)
  - Discovery Park, Scoping, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 66/8)
  - Gas Works Park Clippings, 1972 (Box-folder 66/9)
  - Gas Works Park Drawings, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 66/10)
  - Gas Works Park Position, 1984 (Box-folder 66/11)
  - Gas Works Park Reports - Development, 1970-1984 (Box-folder 66/12)
  - Gas Works Park Reports, 1984 (Box-folder 66/13)
  - Gas Works Park Soils Test, Information and Correspondence, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 66/14)
  - Green Lake Restoration Study, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 66/15)
  - Parks Dept Operating Fund - Open Space, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 66/16)
  - Outdoor Recreation Area Accessibility Surveys, undated (Box-folder 66/17)
  - Outdoor Recreation Area Accessibility Surveys, undated (Box-folder 66/18)
  - Outdoor Recreation Area Accessibility Surveys, undated (Box-folder 66/19)
  - Outdoor Recreation Area Accessibility Surveys, undated (Box-folder 66/20)
  - Outdoor Recreation Area Accessibility Surveys, 1971 (Box-folder 66/21)
  - Property Acquisition - Letters to Property Owners, 1969 (Box-folder 66/22)
  - Urban Beautification Program, 1966 (Box-folder 67/1)
  - Urban Beautification Program, 1967 (Box-folder 67/2)
  - Urban Beautification Program, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 67/3)
  - Urban Beautification Application, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 67/4)
  - Urban Beautification General Correspondence, 1969 (Box-folder 67/5)
  - Urban Beautification Status Reports, 1969 (Box-folder 67/6)
  - Washington Interagency Committee For Outdoor Recreation, Technical Committee, 1969 (Box-folder 67/7)
- Design / Architect's files, 1968-1972
  - Aquarium Planning and Designer, 1971 (Box-folder 67/8)
  - Architectural Consultation, Art Skolnick, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 67/9)
  - Ballard Playfield Lighting, 1971 (Box-folder 67/10)
  - Powell Barnett Park Shelter, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 67/11)
  - Coleman Swimming Pool Rehabilitation, 1971 (Box-folder 67/12)
  - Evans Pool Drawing, 1969 (Box-folder 67/13)
  - First Hill Improvement - 1204 Boren Ave. (Denny House), 1969 (Box-folder 67/14)
  - Gas Works Park Planning, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 67/15)
  - Graphics Designer, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 68/1)
  - Jefferson Park Recreation Center, 1969 (Box-folder 68/2)
  - Leschi Moorage (Incl. Photographs), 1970 (Box-folder 68/3)
  - Magnuson Park (Sand Point) Planning, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 68/4)
  - Mini Parks, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 68/5)
  - Roxhill Playground Building, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 68/6)
  - Service Shops and Yard Project, 1971 (Box-folder 68/7)
  - Swimming Pool Projects, (Incl. Report), 1968-1969 (Box-folder 68/8)
  - West Seattle Golf course Expansion (Incl Drawings), 1970 (Box-folder 68/9)
  - Zoo Master Plan, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 68/10)
  - Zoo Nocturnal House (Bassetti), 1969 (Box-folder 68/11)
  - Zoo Sea Otter Exhibit, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 68/12)
- Drawings (16 reels 35mm microfilm), undated